Guide to the Time Inc. Sports Illustrated Publishing and Business Records 1950s-1993 MS 3009-RG 35
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Advertising Promotion Department Records, 1950s-1987; 28.1 Linear feet in 29 record cartons, 1 document case, and 1 flat box
  - Subseries VI.A. Publicity Director Jane Gilchrist Files, 1950s-1989; 5.5 Linear feet in 6 record cartons and 1 flat box
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: Chicago, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 25)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: Chromes and Dupes (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 26)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: Detroit, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 27)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: Los Angeles, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 28)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: Models and Agencies (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 29)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: Past Covers, 1971-1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 30)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: Peter French? (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 31)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: San Francisco, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 32)
    - Swimsuit Cover: 1988: USA Today, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 33)
    - Swimsuit Tour, 1989 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 34)
    - Wall Street Journal, 1981 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 35)
    - Whitewater Championships (Maryland): 1989 Photo Show, 1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 36)
    - Williams, Doug, 1988 (Offsite-box 4135, Folder 37)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: General, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 1-2)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: April 5 Tennis Match, 1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 3)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: California Media Lists, [1987] (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 4)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Circulation and Rate Increase, 1987 July (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 5)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Correspondence: Women's Sports Foundation and ABC Sports, 1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 6)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: First Release, 1986 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 7)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: July 1987 Issue Summary (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 8)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Kills, 1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 9)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Kim and Jake Workout, 1987 March (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 10)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Magazine Issues, 1986 August-1987 October (Offsite-box 4138, Folder 1-6)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Media and Contacts, 1986 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 11)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Media Lists, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 12-14)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: New York Advance, 1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 15)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Panel Proposal, 1986 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 16)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Pan Am Games Advertising Section, 1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 17)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Pan Am Games Release, 1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 18)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Personnel, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 19)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Philosophy, 1987 June 19 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 20)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (90 sec.). On container: "WSF Philosophy."
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Press Clippings, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 21-23)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Publicity: April-August Issues, 1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 24-28)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: San Francisco, 1986 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 29)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Shoe Guide, 1986 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 30)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Sports Illustrated Meetings, 1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 31)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Subscriber Profile, 1987? (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 32)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Virginia Slims, 1986 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 33)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Women in Sports Day: Press Kit, 1987 (Offsite-box 4137, Folder 34)
  - Subseries VI.C. Promotion Development Manager Kathie-Lee Wilcox Files, 1985-1987; 1 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Organized alphabetically with the arrangement imposed by the archivist.
    Lee Wilcox's files document her work as the Women's Sports & Fitness (WSF) Promotion Director as part of Time Inc.'s trial run working on the magazine. The majority of the files focus on WSF although there are four folders either focused on other events or that aren't clearly related to WSF.
    Records include correspondence, advertiser mailing lists, and press kits. Items of interest include letters to the editor in the General files.
    - Corporate Presentation, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 1)
    - Lavin's, undated (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 2)
    - Skip Barber Racing School, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 3)
    - Sports Marketing News, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 4)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: General, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 5-6)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Account Numbers, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 7)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Ad Age, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 8)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Ad Campaign, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 9)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Advertising Creative, 1986? (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 10)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Ad Directors Memoranda, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 11)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Ad Week, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 12)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Badges, Banner, and Signs, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 13)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Barr, Don: Mailing, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 14)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Bikes, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 15)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Budgets, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 16)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Canyon Ranch, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 17)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Catering, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 18)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Client Mailing Lists, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 19)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Contacts, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 20)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Correspondence, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 21-22)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Direct Mail, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 23)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Editorial Calendar, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 24)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Holiday Mailings, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 25)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Logos and Art Work, 1986? (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 26)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Madison Avenue, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 27)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Marketing and Media Decisions, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 28)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Media Kit, 1987? (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 29-30)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: New York Mailing List, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 31-32)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Nicklaus, Jack: Grand Cypress Resort, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 33)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Office Set-Up and Information, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 34)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Premiums, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 35)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Presentations, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 36)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Prices for Cards, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 37)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness:Publicity, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 38)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Publishers Conference: Banff Springs, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 39-40)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Sales Call, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 41)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Special Events, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 42-44)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Sports Style, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 45)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Spring Shape Up, 1987 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 46)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Spring Shape Up [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R65)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Sprout Mailing, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 47)
    - Women's Sports & Fitness: Virginia Slims, 1986 (Offsite-box 4139, Folder 48-51)
  - Subseries VI.D. Press Information Office Files, 1970-1976; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    The Press Information Office Files contain press releases, photograph files, and weekly reports to the advertising sales staff. The press releases promote sports figure interviews in Sports Illustrated (SI) and other articles, announce SI staffing changes, and report on sports news. Photographs sometimes accompany the press releases. The photograph files contain photographic material of people or events similar to that found in the press release files. Weekly reports include tentative information on issue contents and covers.
    Files for 1973 and 1974 January to April were not found.
    Organized based on the original order which is chronologically with Weekly Friday Reports and Photographs remaining where found between the runs of Press Releases.
    - Press Releases, 1970 January-December (Offsite-box 4144, Folder 1-68)
    - Press Releases, 1971 January-December (Offsite-box 4144, Folder 69-133)
    - Weekly Friday Reports, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 1-2)
    - Press Releases, 1972 January-December (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 3-45)
    - Photographs: Chicago: Western Open Party, 1972? (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 46)
    - Photographs: Father-Son Baseball Clinic, 1972? (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 47)
    - Photographs: Houston Chevy Open, 1972? (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 48)
    - Photographs: Hudson Boat Trip, 1972 (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 49)
    - Photographs: Toy Fair, 1972 (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 50)
    - Press Releases, 1974 May-December (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 51-71)
    - Press Releases, 1975 January-November (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 72-96)
    - Press Releases, 1976 January-December (Offsite-box 4145, Folder 97-121)
  - Subseries VI.E. Advertising Promotion(?) General Files, 1954-1957; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    The General Files tentatively attributed to Advertising Promotion contain market research and research on various industries along with ad campaign presentations. The majority of materials have no indication of the person or department. The majority of memoranda in the files are from Alvin Buchanan, who signs off as "Promotion" with some materials from Robert Hughes, listed as a merchandising specialist in a 1954 Sports Illustrated (SI) staff list, but promoted to SI advertising promotion director by 1960. The date range of the materials indicate these attempts to attract advertisers happened during SI's first few years of operation. Stetson was the first advertiser in SI according to a speech by Hughes in his bio file.
    The General section contain the market research along with fact sheets about (SI), subscriber research, speeches, and other collected material to assist in the promotion of SI. General files also includes a folder of all the empty folders retained that includes names of companies that were possibly targeted as advertisers by SI.
    The Presentation section include scripts of presentations tailored to industries or individual companies to demonstrate why they should advertise in SI. The Pepsi-Cola presentation makes the case for SI as a "merchandising tool." The folder Richard Neale Summary includes a list of 1956 advertisers along with a sales pitch to be used by assistant publisher Neale. On the Move is a general presentation.
    Organized by General and Presentations with alphabetical arrangements within each section. The arrangement was imposed by the archivist. The materials were initially in one box, had no order, and were loose or in folders that were unlabeled or had labels with no relation to the contents. Several folders were initially empty, and the archivist matched up the empty folders with the correct materials within the box. Ultimately empty folders with titles of companies were retained as they may have been targets of promotional presentations.
    - General: Empty Folders, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 1)
    - General: Air Travel: Report of a survey Conducted Among Overseas Air Passengers Departing From N.Y. International Airport, 1954 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 2)
    - General: Appliance Research, 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 3)
    - General: Articles: Short Stops, 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 4)
    - General: Automotive Industry, 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 5)
    - General: Canadian Club, 1957 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 6)
    - General: Fact Sheets, circa 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 7-8)
    - General: Filler Ads, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 9)
    - General: Market Research, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 10)
    - General: Professional Conventions Speeches, 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 11)
    - General: Readership Statistics, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 12-13)
    - General: Round-ups of Promotion Material, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 14)
    - General: Schlitz/Carlings, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 15)
    - General: Ski Letter, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 16)
    - General: Sports Quiz, 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 17)
    - General: Sports Quotes, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 18)
    - General: Sports and Vacation Show, 1955 March (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 19)
    - General: Subscriber Research and Analysis, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 20-21)
    - General: Walter(?) Letter, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 22)
    - Presentations: American Airlines, 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 23-24)
    - Presentations: Appliance/RCA, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 25)
    - Presentations: Automotive/Appliances, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 26-27)
    - Presentations: Brylcreem, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 28)
    - Presentations: B.W. Harris Manufacturing, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 29)
    - Presentations: Cooper's Show (Timely Clothes), circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 30)
    - Presentations: Douglas Aircraft Company, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 31)
    - Presentations: Dunlop Tires, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 32)
    - Presentations: Dupont: Orlon, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 33)
    - Presentations: Energy, 1956 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 34)
    - Presentations: General Tire, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 35)
    - Presentations: Grand Marnier, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 36)
    - Presentations: Greenbrier? (Men's clothing), 1956? (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 37)
    - Presentations: Gudebrod, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 38)
    - Presentations: Hathaway, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 39)
    - Presentations: Herbert Tareyton (Cigarettes), circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 40)
    - Presentations: Horrocks-Ibbotson (Fishing), circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 41)
    - Presentations: Jantzen, circa 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 42-43)
    - Presentations: Kaywoodie Pipes, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 44)
    - Presentations: Keith's Show (Amateur Wrestling Association), circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 45)
    - Presentations: Leisure Market/Louis Goldsmith, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 46)
    - Presentations: Lincoln Continental, 1955-circa 1956 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 47-48)
    - Presentations: Lockheed Corporation (Aircraft), circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 49)
    - Presentations: Moyer Slacks, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 50)
    - Presentations: National Brewing Company, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 51)
    - Presentations: Nettleton (Shoes), circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 52)
    - Presentations: On the Move, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 53-54)
    - Presentations: Peck and Peck, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 55)
    - Presentations: Pedwin (Shoes), [1955] (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 56)
    - Presentations: Pepsi-Cola, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 57)
    - Presentations: Plymouth, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 58)
    - Presentations: Realist (Cameras), circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 59)
    - Presentations: Regional, circa 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 60-62)
    - Presentations: Richard Neale Summary, circa 1956 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 63)
    - Presentations: Sabene (Airlines?), circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 64)
    - Presentations: Schenley, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 65)
    - Presentations: Scott-Atwater, 1957 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 66)
    - Presentations: Spalding, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 67)
    - Presentations: Studebaker, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 68)
    - Presentations: Suave, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 69)
    - Presentations: White Stag and Bantamac, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 70)
    - Presentations: Wollensak, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 71)
    - Presentations: Women's Show, 1956 (Offsite-box 4140, Folder 72)
- Series V. Merchandising Working File, 1953-1957; 2.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons and 1 flat box
  The Merchandising Working File documents the efforts of the Merchandising Department to place displays promoting Sports Illustrated (SI) in retail stores and coordinating events promoting SI. Records come from various staff of the Merchandising Department including merchandising manager George Trescher; Eleanor Lambert, owner of Eleanor Lambert Inc. Publicity, contracted for SI's first year; West Coast merchandising representative Marjorie Kessler; and merchandising representatives Ruth Lieder, Mary Mitchell, Eleanor Montville, Alberta Scribner, and Fred Smith. Extensive correspondence from Trescher is throughout the files. Files for assistant publishers Richard "Dick" Neale and Harry Phillips and advertising promotion manager Bill Scherman include memoranda to them reporting on Merchandising's efforts. The Merchandising Working File also contains some of the earliest correspondence from founding managing editor Sidney James.
  Records include correspondence to and from retailers, form letters promoting the magazine, memoranda from merchandising represenatives reporting on their activities and retailers' responses, press releases, lists of retailers contacted, and a few photographs of store displays featuring SI. Samples include posters, brochures, press kits and other specialized printed material promoting SI or retailers mentioning SI.
  The presentation scripts from Merchandising are very similar in structure to those in Advertising Promotion although trying to place SI displays in retail stores instead of trying to place ads in SI. "The Sporting Look" refers to the weekly fashion feature in SI, and this feature was used to convince retailers to include SI in their merchandising plans. Suggestions to retailers are detailed in the Launching Letter to Retailers.
  Organized alphabetically based on the original loose order. Using the original titles, folders from H to Y were present indicating that there might be records A to G not present. Retitling of some folders created folder titles earlier in the alphabet.
  - Calpatio Company: Shady Lady, 1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 1)
  - First Cover Promotion, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 2)
  - Haspel Suit Promotion, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 3)
  - James, Sidney, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 4)
  - J.W. Robinson: SUC, 1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 5)
  - Kessler, Marjorie, 1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 6)
  - Lambert, Eleanor, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 7-8)
  - Launching: Department Store Correspondence, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 9)
  - Launching: Letter to Retailers and List, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 10)
  - Launching: Orders and Lists, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 11)
  - Launching: Package Number 1, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 12)
  - Launching: Promotion Plan Letter, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 13)
  - Launching: Samples, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 14)
  - Launching: Travels: Telegrams, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 15)
  - Legal: Publicity Releases, 1956 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 16)
  - "Let's Go Hunting" Photographs, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 17)
  - Lieder, Ruth, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 18)
  - Long Island Liquor Laws, 1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 19)
  - Los Angeles Office, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 20)
  - Lynbrook, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 21)
  - Marine Merchandising, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 22)
  - Men's Apparel Forum, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 23)
  - Merchandising (General), 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 24-25)
  - Merchandising Programs, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Requests for Display Material, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 27)
  - Mitchell, Mary, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 28)
  - Montville, Eleanor, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 29)
  - National Association of Retail Clothiers and Furnishers (NARCF) Convention, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 30)
  - National Sporting Goods Association (NSGA), 1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 31-32)
  - Neale, Richard, 1953-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 33)
  - Neiman Marcus, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 34)
  - New York Dress Institute, 1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 35)
  - Phillips, H.H.S. (Harry), 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 36)
  - Presentations, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 37-39)
  - Ranchero Tie-ins, 1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 40)
  - Results, 1954 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 41)
  - Riviera Kit, 1955 (Offsite-box 4141, Folder 42)
  - Rodder's: Fiesta Siesta, 1955 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 1)
  - Roland's: Sports and Vacation Carnival, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 2)
  - Roos Bros, 1954 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 3)
  - Saks Fifth Avenue, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 4)
  - Sales Convention: Myrtle Beach, 1955 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 5)
  - Sales Convention: Myrtle Beach, 1955 (Offsite-box 4147, Folder 4)
  - San Francisco Office, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 6)
  - Scherman, Bill, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 7)
  - Scribner, Alberta, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 8)
  - Scruggs Vandervoort-St. Lous: Sports and Vacation Carnival, 1955 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 9)
  - Sea Shells, 1955 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 10)
  - Selber Bros: Sports and Vacation Carnival, 1955 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Fred, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 12)
  - Special Merchandising Samples, 1956 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 13-20)
  - Sports and Vacation Carnival, 1955 (Offsite-box 4142, Folder 21)
  - The Sporting Look: General, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 1-2)
  - The Sporting Look: Country Corduroy Suits, 1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 3)
  - The Sporting Look: Fashion Releases, 1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 4)
  - The Sporting Look: Palm Springs Story, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 5)
  - The Sporting Look: Sport Jacket Pictures, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 6)
  - Sportsman of the Year, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 7)
  - Sterling Advertising Agency, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 8)
  - Store Contact Letters, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 9)
  - Store Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 10-14)
  - Subscription Desks: Sporting Goods Dealers and Pro Shops, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 15)
  - Subscription Thank Yous: Blurb Letters, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 16)
  - Tobé Stores, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 17)
  - Trade Ads, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 18)
  - Trade Information Bulletin Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 19)
  - Travel, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 20)
  - Trescher, George, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 21)
  - U.S. Information Agency, 1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 22)
  - Wanamaker, 1955-1957 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 23)
  - Washington Ad Club Fashion Show, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 24)
  - Weitz, John, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 25)
  - Westbury Country Galleries Exhibit, 1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 26)
  - Women and Sport, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 27)
  - Women's Show Television Kit, circa 1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 28)